Christmas Lodge is a drama, family, tv movie film directed by Terry Ingram.
Mary Tobin has wonderful memories of family gatherings at the Christmas Lodge.
When she arrives for a weekend vacation, she quickly realizes that the
lodge that she loves has fallen into serious disrepair.
With a lack of funds and a looming deadline, she not only restores the
Christmas lodge's charm but finds love along the way.
Mary, played by Erin Karpluk.
Jack, played by Michael Shanks.
Yolanda, played by Rukiya Bernard.
Betty, played by Rebecca Toolan.
Grampa, played by John Innes.
Kathy, played by Victoria Banks.
Many Christmas stories have been adapted to feature films and TV specials,
and have been broadcast and repeated many times on television.
Since the popularization of home video in the 1980s, these films are sold
and re-sold every year during the holiday shopping season.
Many television networks, film studios, and production companies, such as cable television channels Hallmark and Lifetime, produce and
release new Christmas-themed films every year during or around December, all with variations of similar plots and themes.
Additionally, films revolving around the Nativity story of Christmas are regularly
produced such as The Nativity Story (2006) and The Star (2017).
One film that has become the flashpoint for "Is this a Christmas movie or not?" debates is Die Hard (1988), with some viewing the film as a
Christmas movie intertwined with an action genre setting or a film that is simply set around the Christmas and holiday season.
The film explores themes of holiday, lodge, christmas.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.